liverpool-degrees.com 2016-06-01

# Privacy Policy | University of Liverpool Online

Laureate Online Education presents this Statement of Privacy to you in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The following information discloses Laureate Online Education’s data collection, maintaining, processing and transfer practices with relation to this website [www.university-liverpool-online.com](http://www.university-liverpool-online.com/). 

Laureate Online Education values each and every one of its website’s visitors and their privacy. However, please note that this website may contain links to other websites. Naturally, Laureate Online Education is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. 

**What we do with the personal information we collect**

The registration process to services provided by Laureate Online Education on its web-site requires you to provide it with your personal information. Such information, as well as other information which may be gathered while you are visiting Laureate Online Education’s website, may be used by Laureate Online Education and its affiliates (including Laureate Education, Inc. and Laureate International Universities network members ) to various ends, such as: (a) to contact you in order to confirm your registration; (b) to provide you with further information about our programmes at Liverpool and other Laureate affiliated institutions ; (c) to execute and apply your agreement(s) with Laureate Online Education; (d) to properly administer Laureate Online Education activities; (e) to contact consumers for marketing and operational purposes as you may receive telephone or email contact from us with information regarding special promotions, new products and services, or upcoming events and (f) to allow Laureate Online Education to fully provide you with the services offered by it.

Laureate Online Education does not sell or trade its website’s visitor’s personal information, such as names, addresses and mailing lists. Laureate Online Education will not share or divulge your address, telephone number, e-mail address, or any other personal information collected at its web-site to advertisers, sponsors or any other third parties, without your informed consent, except as specifically stated below, or where such disclosure is required by law or governmental request, or is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with any legal process; (b) execute and apply your agreement(s) with Laureate Online Education; and - (c) protect the rights, property, or safety of Laureate Online Education, its employees, agents, representatives and customers, and the public.

**With whom we share the personal information**

For the proper administration of Laureate Online Education activities and in order to allow Laureate Online Education to fully provide you with the various services contained therein, you hereby expressly permit Laureate Online Education to collect, maintain and process any of your personal data, or a part thereof, including without limitation any information protected by the Dutch Data Protection Act, the European Union Directive on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and the free movement thereof, or by any other applicable legislation, in any computer network as Laureate Online Education deems appropriate. This Policy also complies with the Safe Harbor Principles as agreed upon between the United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission. Consistent with its commitment to protect personal privacy, Laureate adheres to these Safe Harbor Principles, which can be found at: <http://export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

For these purposes, you further expressly permit Laureate Online Education to transfer such data, or a part thereof, to any computer network(s), including without limitation that of the University of Liverpool and of Laureate Online Education representatives worldwide, in the Netherlands, the United Kingdom, the USA or any other country as Laureate Online Education deems appropriate to provide you services. You understand that the level of data protection in countries outside the European Union may not be equal to the level of data protection under Dutch law and that Laureate Online Education will take adequate measures to ensure an adequate level of protection of the personal data during and after the transfer.

**Personal information modification**

You are hereby informed that you have a right to access and correct any of your personal data held by Laureate Online Education at any time, by contacting Laureate Online Education at Haarlerbergpark River Building 2nd Floor, Haarlerbergweg 23C, 1101 CH Amsterdam Z.O The Netherlands or at [webmaster@liverpool-online.com](mailto:webmaster@liverpool-online.com). 

**Security of personal information**

Our personal information is stored on servers, which are protected by security measures to protect the data against access by unauthorized individuals. 

**Governing law**

This Statement of Privacy is governed by the laws of the Netherlands, without effect to any conflict of laws rules. For any dispute arising from this Statement, you shall submit exclusively to the jurisdiction of the competent court in Amsterdam, The Netherlands. If any provision in this Statement is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, then such provision shall be construed, as nearly as possible, to reflect the intention of Laureate Online Education. 

**Links**

Laureate Online Education may provide you with links to other sites. Please be aware that Laureate Online Education is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. Laureate Online Education does not endorse them or make any representations about them or any information, services, products or materials found on them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites through links, we strongly encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**Cookies**

When you use our websites, our web server logs your Internet Protocol (IP) address to register a link between your computer/device and our website. We do so by using cookies. We do not collect personal data (E.g. Name, Address, etc) in this manner, however people wanting to request more information can supply their personal details via our Information Request Form which will enable us to contact them.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or device when you visit a website. Cookies are used by all websites and have a variety of functions, primarily:

  * Allowing the website to function as intended and in a secure manner
  * Enabling us to monitor performance, functionality and usability of the website
  * Improving user experience of the website by remembering information entered by a site visitor
  * Improving experience by displaying information of relevance to you

**The cookies we use**

 **1\. Necessary cookies**  
These types of cookies allow you to move our around our website and utilize the features as intended. These cookies will only be placed by Laureate Online Education's websites and not by third parties.

Our necessary cookies will:  

  * Enable site functionality
  * Detect the best settings for the device you are using

Our necessary cookies will not:  

  * Store any behavioural information
  * Send any information to third parties

**2\. Performance cookies**  
These cookies help us to improve our website(s) and performance by telling us how people use each page, most commonly viewed pages, recurring errors, etc. The majority of our performance cookies are placed by Laureate Online Education. We also place cookies by third parties, such as companies who provide analytical information to us.

Our performance cookies will:  

  * Identifying errors within the website, allowing us to improve it
  * Help us understand user interaction
  * Enable the website to run quicker and more efficiently

Our performance cookies will not:  

  * Store personal information beyond your current visit

**3\. Customisation cookies**  
The purpose of these cookies is to store any personal settings (E.g. Font size) that you may have chosen on the site. The majority of our performance cookies are placed by Laureate Online Education. We also place information by third parties, such as companies who provide specialist information to us.

Our customisation cookies will:  

  * Store preferences that you select, such as font sizes or volume level

Our customisation cookies will not:

  * Store any of your secure information 

**Consent**

By using our website you are consenting to the use of cookies. We recommend you do not change the cookies settings as this can affect the performance of the website. 

If you feel you wish to change your cookies settings you can do so in the cookie settings of your web browser. Each browser differs from one to the next so view your browser's help section to learn how to make changes. 

Cookie Type | Purpose  | Cookie  
---|---|---  
Necessary | To help keep your browsing session private | ASP.NET_SessionId  
Necessary | To keep your internet session running smoothly | ASP.NET_SessionId  
Performance | To help us track referrals and pay commission when earned | ictf_il490, ictf_in490, ictf_master, sc_pview_shuser   
Customisation | To remember the pages you've seen so you can navigate back | ASP.NET_SessionId, HasAccptedCookieLaw   
  
**Contact us**

Should you have any questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please do not hesitate to contact 

Laureate Online Education  
Haarlerbergweg 23C  
1101 CH Amsterdam Z.O.  
The Netherlands

### Request Information

* * *

* * *
